var questions=[
    {
        num : 1,
        question : "",
        answer : "Philippines",
        options : [
            "Yemen",
            "Iraq",
            "Malaysia",
            "Philippines",
        ]
    },
    {
    num : 2,
    question : "",
    answer : "Vietnam",
    options : [
        "Uzbekistan",
        "Vietnam",
        "Iraq",
        "Jordan",
    ]
},
{
    num : 3,
    question : "",
    answer : "Thailand",
    options : [
        "Thailand",
        "Egypt",
        "Taiwan",
        "Qatar",
    ]
},
{
    num : 4,
    question : "",
    answer : "Myanmar",
    options : [
        "Kuwait",
        "Myanmar",
        "Georgia",
        "Israel",
    ]
},
{
    num : 5,
    question : "",
    answer : "Turkey",
    options : [
        "Maldives",
        "Singapore",
        "Turkey",
        "Bahrain",
    ]
},
{
    num : 6,
    question : "",
    answer : "Afghanistan",
    options : [
        "Tajikistan",
        "Kyrgyzstan",
        "Afghanistan",
        "Vietnam",
    ]
},
{
    num : 7,
    question : "",
    answer : "Uzbekistan",
    options : [
        "Malaysia",
        "Cambodia",
        "Uzbekistan",
        "Taiwan",
    ]
},
{
    num : 8,
    question : "",
    answer : "Taiwan",
    options : [
        "Palestine",
        "Timor-Leste",
        "Qatar",
        "Taiwan",
    ]
},
{
    num : 9,
    question : "",
    answer : "Hong kong",
    options : [
        "Hong kong",
        "Laos",
        "Cambodia",
        "Azerbaijan",
    ]
},
{
    num : 10,
    question : "",
    answer : "Kuwait",
    options : [
        "Kuwait",
        "Qatar",
        "Lebanon",
        "Brunei",
    ]
},
{
    num : 11,
    question : "",
    answer : "Singapore",
    options : [
        "Bahrain",
        "Maldives",
        "Singapore",
        "Qatar",
    ]
},
{
    num : 12,
    question : "",
    answer : "Kyrgyzstan",
    options : [
        "Kyrgyzstan",
        "Iraq",
        "Uzbekistan",
        "Turkmenistan",
    ]
},
{
    num : 13,
    question : "",
    answer : "Cambodia",
    options : [
        "Mongolia",
        "Afghanistan",
        "Cambodia",
        "Vietnam",
    ]
},
{
    num : 14,
    question : "",
    answer : "SaudiArabia",
    options : [
        "Oman",
        "SaudiArabia",
        "Iran",
        "Russia",
    ]
},
{
    num : 15,
    question : "",
    answer : "Mongolia",
    options : [
        "Syria",
        "Mongolia",
        "Philippines",
        "Laos",
    ]
},
{
    num : 16,
    question : "",
    answer : "Jordan",
    options : [
        "Jordan",
        "Armenia",
        "Timor-Leste",
        "Israel",
    ]
},
{
    num : 17,
    question : "",
    answer : "Brunei",
    options : [
        "Georgia",
        "Bahrain",
        "Kyrgyzstan",
        "Brunei",
    ]
},
{
    num : 18,
    question : "",
    answer : "Maldives",
    options : [
        "Maldives",
        "Thailand",
        "Uzbekistan",
        "Turkey",
    ]
},
{
    num : 19,
    question : "",
    answer : "Tajikistan",
    options : [
        "Laos",
        "Tajikistan",
        "Cambodia",
        "Vietnam",
    ]
}
];